<resources>
    <string name="hello">Welcome to SWOT Analysis</string>
    <string name="hello1">        Ram Consultancy services welcomes you to this session of knowing the self in you and
tries to harness your internal and external reosources.\n
      When you have some legal issues, you seek the advise of some legal consultants or lawyers and in the case of
Finance either saving or for loan, you consult some experts. \n
        You even depend on Astrologers in certain cases.\n
        But when you have some problem of managing your business or profession you take your
own decisions based on your knowledge and experience.\n





You dont know to whom to approach. You may remember that even the great emperors
including Devendra  had gurus to advise them.
In this connection we introduce this App which is a handy tool to be with you to help you
in real situation. This will take you to professional Mentros and ensures
your success.
We here use the best available tool for problem solving and that is the SWOT analysis with the help of
Information technology.\n
        Then What is SWOT Analysis?\n


        A SWOT analysis is a structured planning method used to evaluate the
        strengths, weaknesses, opportunities and threats involved in a project or in a business
        venture. \n
        A SWOT analysis can be carried out for a product, place, industry or person. \n
        It involves specifying the objective of the business venture or project and identifying
        the internal and external factors that are favorable and unfavorable to
        achieve that objective.!</string>
    <string name="hello2">When to use SWOT \n
•  Explore new solutions to problems \n
•  Identify barriers that will limit goals/objectives \n
•  Decide on direction that will be most effective \n
• Reveal possibilities and limitations for change \n
• To revise plans to best navigate systems, communities, and organizations \n
• As a brainstorming and recording device as a means of communication \n
• To enhance “credibility of interpretation” to be utilized in presentation to leaders or key supporters \n</string>
    <string name="hello3">How to  use SWOT \n
•   Decide on the objective of your SWOT analysis \n
•   Research your self,business, industry and market \n
•   List your business strengths \n
•   List your business weaknesses \n
•   List potential opportunities  \n
•   List potential threats \n
•   Establish priorities from the SWOT \n
•   Develop a strategy to address issues in the SWOT\n
•   Consult a Mentor \n</string>
    <string name="mentor1">For a Free Advice,You may Please contact @9447466395 \n
        Visit  @ramconsultancy.in</string>
    <string name="app_name">Ram Consultancy</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
